[{"answer": "So are you going to my friend's party this weekend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend really wants to go", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " I said you know what I do  when I want to relax? The Jumble. Hey do you make a book of Jumbles", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Going deaf", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "After this go back to city for a ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "794 Bleeker the party's my friend. Tom my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'm not", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Can't hear a thing", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You're giving me the", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You're", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I was just trying to..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'm sure you do it very well", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "But I thought things were going great", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Did she say why", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Get out of here. I didn't see any cameras there", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Cracks? What were they saying", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yes I do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Well I can't now, my friend's going to be there", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Oh.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well I was just going to wander the streets. Wouldn't want to tag along with you or anything", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Well", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "\"Yes sweep", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "my friend says", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Cut it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Cut it", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend says", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "my friend is saying", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Cut it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Lip-Reader.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Cut it.   Would you stop signing? She said", "qsentId": 30}]